{
    "subject": "resource/The_Suite_Life_on_Deck",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Doc_Shaw",
    "human_readable": "The Suite Life on Deck stars Doc Shaw.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8834671378135681,
            "question": "What is the name of Doc Shaw's character in 'The Suite Life on Deck'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7818173170089722,
            "question": "Who stars in the show 'The Suite Life on Deck'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6835880279541016,
            "question": "Who are some other actors in 'The Suite Life on Deck'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5943582057952881,
            "question": "Where does 'The Suite Life on Deck' take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5799523591995239,
            "question": "Is 'The Suite Life on Deck' a comedy show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5746598839759827,
            "question": "What type of show is 'The Suite Life on Deck'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5703423619270325,
            "question": "Name an actor from 'The Suite Life on Deck'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38337209820747375,
            "question": "What is Doc Shaw known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23682305216789246,
            "question": "Is Doc Shaw in a Disney show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20209766924381256,
            "question": "Has Doc Shaw been in any other TV shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Suite Life on Deck stars Doc Shaw.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7640_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Doc Shaw in a Disney show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7640_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Doc Shaw known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7640_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name an actor from 'The Suite Life on Deck'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7640_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7640_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention Doc Shaw as a star in the Disney Channel series \"The Suite Life on Deck\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Doc Shaw's roles, including his starring role in \"The Suite Life on Deck,\" which directly supports the statement that \"The Suite Life on Deck stars Doc Shaw.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}